# Pablo Antonio Pérez Chavira

## Front End Developer

Guadalajara, Jalisco

pablo.ceti.96@hotmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/pabloprz

**™** github.com/PRZ96

#### About me

I am a passionate front-end developer with a strong affinity for creating dynamic web applications that adhere to the Model-View-Controller (MVC) architecture. My dedication to crafting intuitive user interfaces and optimizing user experiences drives my commitment to the field of web development. I am also open to exploring and learning about new technologies and domains to broaden my skills and knowledge.

### **Skills**

- HTML
- · CSS / SASS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Tailwind CSS

- React
- Vue.js
- Figma
- Photoshop / Illustrator
- Git (Github / Bitbucket)

- Laravel
- Gulp
- Agile / Waterfall Method
- C / C++ / Python
- English (Advanced)

## **Experience**

## HallMG - Zapopan, Jalisco

#### Front End Developer (Jul 2022 - Present)

- Developed user interfaces using Bootstrap, CSS, SCSS, and Laravel.
- Collaborated with the design team to create intuitive and visually appealing user experiences.
- Implemented responsive design techniques to ensure optimal performance across devices.
- Diagnosed and resolved technical issues related to software and hosting.
- · Developed and maintained software applications to improve customer experience and efficiency.
- · Suggest changes to improve UX/UI and stability.
- · Tested new features and bug-fixes.

## Instituto Anahuacalli - Zapopan, Jalisco

#### IT Responsible (Jun 2021 - Jun 2022)

- · Managed Google Admin to configure and control college's services, user accounts, devices, and access.
- Provided technical support to customers or end-users, troubleshooting hardware and software issues, diagnosing problems, and finding solutions.

## Promomedios de Occidente - Zapopan, Jalisco

#### IT Assistant (Apr 2015 - Jul 2018)

- Repaired computers to ensure optimal performance, including hardware and software upgrades, troubleshooting, and maintenance.
- Trained sales team members in specific software to enhance their productivity and sales performance.
- Provided technical support to the company's team members.

# **Relevant Projects**

- UnidadMedicaSante.com.mx Medical Unit Landing Page
- LevelAgencyModels.com Models Agency Landing Page

## **Education**

#### **MBA** in Finance

Universidad del Valle de México - Zapopan, Jalisco (Apr 2021 - Apr 2023)

Relevant coursework includes financial analysis, financial markets, investment management, corporate finance, risk management, strategic
marketing and leadership.

## **Mechatronics Engineering**

Centro de Enseñanza Técnica Industrial (Aug 2016 - Jul 2020)

- · Graduated as the top-performing student of the program, achieving the highest grade of the generation.
- · Relevant coursework includes mechanical design, electronics, control systems, programming, and robotics.

## **Graphic Design Diploma**

CAAV Universidad de Medios Audiovisuales (Jan 2018 - Jun 2018)

· Relevant coursework includes graphic design fundamentals, typography and layout, digital imaging, branding and identity design.

## Informatics and Computing Technologist

Centro de Enseñanza Técnica Industrial (Aug 2012 - Jul 2016)

- · Focused on software development.
- Relevant coursework includes programming languages, algorithms and data structures, software engineering, and database management.

# **Professional Development**

#### **Desarrollo Web**

Coderhouse (Oct 2023)

• Credential ID 654692ea7cdb9b44a88cc24b

#### Bootstrap 5 y SASS - La Guía Práctica

Udemy (May 2023)

Credential ID UC-22816b98-1470-432b-9337-58ce7e646568

#### GIT+GitHub: Todo un sistema de control de versiones de cero

Udemy (Nov 2022)

Credential ID UC-e5edb7f4-61da-4df6-b523-a3120673d6c9

### AI-900T00: Microsoft Azure AI Fundamentals

CompuEducación (Jul 2022)

• Credential ID X19-56827

## Lean Six Sigma Yellow Belt

HR SMART INSTITUTE - HRSI® (Jun 2019)

• Credential ID CSSYB-HRSI-000161

## DAT208x: Introduction to Python for Data Science

Microsoft - edX (Sep 2017)

Credential ID 73412f023f6848e6856019b9189ec0cf